(Howard:)Hey, Stuart, I got you
a little souvenir from my trip to space.
Wow, Howard, that's very nice of you.
(Leonard:)Yeah, maybe. Open it first.
(Howard:)It's my official NASA portrait.
"To Stuart, your comic book store
is out of this world...
...just like the guy in this picture was."
(Sheldon:)For the record,
he also thinks that Walgreens...
...and the drycleaners
are out of this world.
That's not true. At Walgreens I was "over
the moon" for their store-brand antacids.
(Raj:)I see you're getting ready
for your Halloween party.
(Stuart:)Yeah, it's my annual attempt
to meet women.
(Stuart:)Ninth time's the charm.
Would you like me to help? I have a certain
je ne sais quoi when it comes to soirees.
(Stuart:)Thanks, but I can't afford je ne sais quoi.
How much forjust quoi?
(Raj:)Don't worry about money,
I'll take care of it.
- Really?
- Yeah, you'll love it.
(Raj:)Ain't no party like a Koothra-party.
Ha-ha-ha.
(Howard:)You know what wasn't a party?
That hotel in Kazakhstan...
(Howard:)...they put you up in before the launch.
You'd think you'd get one porn channel.
Have you noticed Howard can take any topic
and use it to remind you he went to space?
(Sheldon:)Interesting hypothesis.
(Sheldon:)Let's apply the scientific method.
Perform an experiment.
(Leonard:)Okay. Hey, Howard.
(Leonard:)- Thoughts on where we should get dinner?
- Anywhere but the space station.
(Howard:)On a good day,
dinner was a bag full of meatloaf.
(Howard:)But, hey, you don't go there for the food,
you go there for the view.
That's fascinating.
I'm gonna see if I can duplicate it.
(Sheldon:)Howard, I've always thought the lemon
was an underrated fruit.
(Sheldon:)Care to weigh in?
(Howard:)Not really.
- Oh, well.
- People say the Soyuz capsule's a lemon...
Yeah, but, hey,
that baby got me to space and back.